欢笑之声遍世间，
Jollity, forever shown;
乐道之者却鲜见。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真实的诚挚，
Sincerity and emphasis,
仅在欢乐中看见。
so truly seen in happiness.
人的心灵，可以苟且，可以突出
With one mind, we can make, we can live
人的生命，可以接受，可以付出
With a life, one can take, one can give
我们欢笑，分享著我们的一切
We rejoice, lending all we possess
人的声音，可以如尘，可以如钟
With a voice, one can lift or depress
欢笑之声遍世间，
Jollity, forever shown;
乐道之者却鲜见。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真实的诚挚，
Sincerity and emphasis,
仅在欢乐中看见。
so truly seen in happiness.
在欢笑中
In happiness
这场大梦不允许一点怨气
In this dream, there is no room for spite
但却好像是我自己的决定
Still it seems, only I can decide
我迷了路，但却不用待在世间
I am lost, but am free of the world
在我眼里，那是冰冷，那是苍凉
For outside, all is bleak, all is cold
欢笑之声遍世间，
Jollity, forever shown;
乐道之者却鲜见。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真实的诚挚，
Sincerity and emphasis,
仅在欢乐中看见。
so truly seen in happiness.
欢笑之声遍世间，
Jollity, forever shown;
乐道之者却鲜见。
path of joy, so few have known.
那份真实的诚挚，
Sincerity and emphasis,
仅在欢乐中看见。
so truly seen in happiness.
在欢笑中
In happiness